Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part One
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph collection, part one
1718-1955
OSB MSS 135
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
21.07
(65 boxes)
Collection of several thousand clipped autographs, franked envelopes, and autographed notes and letters by British notables, mostly from the nineteenth century. The collection is particularly strong in members of the British royal family; members of the nobility and gentry; politicians; churchmen, including missionaries and members of the Anglican hierarchy; and artists, actors, authors and journalists.
Levy, Edward G., 1898-1990
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy, 1980.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
EDWARD G. LEVY (1898-1990)
Edward G. Levy was born in New Haven, Connecticut on October 21, 1898 and educated in the city's public schools. He received his LL.B. from Boston University in 1921 and joined his brother, Herman L. Levy, in his law practice in New Haven, specializing in theatrical law. Levy married Hortense Rosenblatt in 1926; their son Charles Joseph was born in 1935.
In May 1938, Levy was charged with participating in a conspiracy with 22 others, including the Mayor of Waterbury, to defraud that city of more than $1,000,000. He pled guilty and turned state's evidence; the New York Times reported on February 4, 1939 that Levy admitted under cross-examination that he had been expelled from Yale University for cheating and that he had worked as a lobbyist "for various interests" before becoming involved with the conspirators. After his cooperation, Levy received a sentence of one year in jail.
In his later years, Levy became known as a dime novel collector and historian, and he and his wife amassed substantial autograph collections as well, donating dime novels and manuscripts to several universities, including Harvard, New York University, and Yale. The couple maintained residences in Woodbridge, Connecticut, and Palm Beach, Florida, where they were members of the Palm Beach Country Club. Edward G. Levy died on January 15th, 1990.
Scope and Contents
The Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Collection, Part I consists of several thousand clipped autographs, franked envelopes, autographed photographs, and autograph notes and letters by nineteenth century British notables. The majority of the items date from the last half of the nineteenth century and include autographs of members of the British royal family; hundreds of members of the nobility and gentry; politicians, especially members of Parliament; churchmen, including missionaries and members of the Anglican hierarchy; artists, authors, actors, and journalists; and military men, in particular holders of the Victoria Cross.
Actors -- Great Britain -- Autographs; Authors, English -- Autographs; Autographs -- Great Britain; Clergy -- Great Britain -- Autographs; Gentry -- Great Britain -- Autographs; Nobility -- Great Britain -- Autographs; Politicians -- Great Britain -- Autographs; Royal family -- Great Britain -- Autographs; Levy, Edward G., 1898-1990
- Alphabetical Files, 1710-1955; 21.07; (65 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Alphabetical Files contains several thousand autographs, alphabetically arranged by signer. The name forms used by the Levys are the forms included in this list. Generally, members of the nobility are referred to by their highest titles; married women are referred to by their married names; and actors are listed under their stage names, but there are exceptions. Many individuals are represented by more than one autograph. In these cases, there are no item counts, but the date span for the contents of the folder has been given.
  - Abbey, Edwin Austin, 1852-1911, 1883, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, Evelyn, 1843-1901, 1888-89 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abercorn, James Hamilton, Duke of, 1811-1885, 1866-90, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abercorn, James Hamilton, Duke of, 1838-1913, 1886-94, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abercorn, Lady Mary Anna (Curzon) Hamilton, Duchess of, d. 1929, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aberdare, Henry Austin Bruce, Baron, 1815-1895, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Aberdeen, George Hamilton Gordon, earl of, 1784-1860, 1839-45, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aberdeen and Temair, Ishbel Gordon, Marchioness of, 1857-1939, 1893-1900 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Abergavenny, Caroline (Van-den-Bempde- Johnstone) Nevill, Countess of, 1826- 1892, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Acland, Henry W. (Henry Wentworth), 1815-1900, 1860-65 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Acton, Marie (Arco-Valley) Acton, Baroness, d. 1923, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adair, Sir Hugh Edward, Bart., 1815- 1902, 1849 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adams, William Henry Davenport, 1828- 1891, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Addington, Eleanor Anne (wife of Henry Unwin Addington, 1790-1870), undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adelaide, Queen Consort of William IV, 1792-1849, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Adler, Hermann Nathan, 1839-1911, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Adolphus, Marquess of Cambridge, 1868- 1927, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Adolphus Frederick, Duke of Cambridge, 1774-1850, 1805-50, undated (Box 1, Folder 18-20)
  - Adye, John, Sir, 1857-1930, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Aflalo, Frederick G. (Frederick George), 1870-1918, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Agnew, Sir Andrew, Bart., 1793-1849, 1840 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Aidé, Charles Hamilton, 1830-1907, 1883, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Aikin, Lucy, 1781-1864, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ailesbury, Ernest Augustus Charles Brudenell-Bruce, Marquess of, 1811- 1886, 1838 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ailesbury, Maria Elizabeth (Tollemache) Brudenell-Bruce, Marchioness of, 1809-1893, 1883, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ainger, Alfred, 1837-1904, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ainley, Henry Hinchliffe, 1879-1945, 1909-29, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ainsworth, William, 1807-1896, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Ainsworth, William Harrison, 1805-1882, 1868, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Akerman, John Yonge, 1806-1873, 1836 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Alamayu, Prince of Abyssinia, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Albani, Emma, Dame, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Albemarle, William Charles Keppel, Earl of, 1772-1849, 1831, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Albemarle, George Thomas Keppel, Earl of, 1799-1891, 1887, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Albemarle, William Coutts Keppel, Earl of, 1832-1894, 1882 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Albert, Prince Consort of Victoria, Queen of Great Britain, 1819-1861 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Albizzi, Count, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Alcester, Frederick Beauchamp Paget Seymour, Baron, 1821-1895, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Alden, William Livingston, 1837-1908, 1903, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Aldenham, Henry Huck Gibbs, Baron, 1819-1907, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Alderson, Edward Hall, Sir, 1787-1857, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Alexander, Sir George, 1858-1918, 1889-94, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Alexandra, Queen, consort of Edward VII, King of Great Britain, 1844-1925, 1899-1918 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Alford, Henry, 1810-1871, 1851-65 (Box 2, Folder 46-47)
  - Alfred Ernest Albert, Duke of Edinburgh, 1844-1900, 1864-95 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Alice, Duchess of Gloucester, 1901- 2004, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Alice, Princess of Great Britain, b. 1883, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Alice Mary Maud, Princess of Great Britain, 1843-1878, 1878, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Alison, Archibald, Sir, 1792-1867, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Alletz, Eliza, 1843 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Allsopp, George Higginson, 1846-1907, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Alma-Tadema, Lawrence, Sir, 1836-1912, 1897, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Alverstone, Richard Everard Webster, Viscount, 1842-1915, 1868-1913 (Box 2, Folder 56-61)
  - Amherst, William Archer Amherst, Earl, 1836-1910, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Amherst, William Amhurst Tyssen- Amherst, Baron, 1835-1909, 1882-96, undated (Box 2, Folder 63-65)
  - Amours, R., undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Ampthill, Odo William Leopold Russell, Baron, 1829-1884, 1880-84, undated (Box 2, Folder 67-68)
  - Ancaster, Gilbert Henry Heathcote- Drummond-Willoughby, Earl of, 1830- 1910, 1877-94, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Anderson, George, 1839 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Anderson, Sir James, 1866 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Angerstein, William, 1857 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Anglesey, Henry William Paget, Marquis of, 1768-1854, 1823, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Ansdell, Richard, 1815-1885, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Anson, G. E., 1812-1849, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Anson, William Reynell, Sir, 1843-1914, 1893-1902 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Ansted, D. T. (David Thomas), 1814-1880, 1847-61 (Box 2, Folder 77-78)
  - Apperley, Charles James, 1778-1843, 1838 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Arbuthnot, Alexander John, Sir, 1822- 1907, 1863-78 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Arbuthnot, G. (George), 1802-1865, 1850 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Arch, Joseph, 1826-1919, 1892, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Argyll, Amelia Maria (Claughton) Anson Campbell, Duchess of, 1844-1894, 1884 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Argyll, Elizabeth Georgiana (Sutherland-Leveson-Gower) Campbell, Duchess of, 1824-1878, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Argyll, George Douglas Campbell, Duke of, 1823-1900, 1854-90, undated (Box 3, Folder 85-89)
  - Argyll, John Douglas Edward Henry Campbell, Duke of, 1777-1847, 1841 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Argyll, John Douglas Sutherland Campbell, Duke of, 1845-1914, 1871-1902, undated (Box 3, Folder 91-93)
  - Armstead, Henry Hugh, 1828-1905, 1845 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Arrow, Sir Frederick, d. 1875, undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Arthur William Patrick Albert, Duke of Connaught and Strathcarn, 1850-1942, 1873-1907, undated (Box 4, Folder 96-99)
  - Ashbourne, Edward Gibson, Baron, 1837- 1913, 1877-1900 (Box 4, Folder 100-101)
  - Ashburnham, Bertram Ashburnham, Earl of, 1797-1878, 1871-90 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Ashburton, Alexander Baring, Baron, 1774-1848, 1841 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Ashby-Sterry, J. (Joseph), d.1917, 1889 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Ashley, Anthony Evelyn Melbourne, 1836-1907, 1862 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Ashley, Mrs. W., undated (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Ashwell, A. R. (Arthur Rawson), 1824- 1879, 1866 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Ashwell, Lena, 1872-1957, 1903, undated (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Asquith, H. H. (Herbert Henry), 1852- 1928, 1889-1920, undated (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Atherton, William, 1806-1864, 1861, undated (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Atholl, George Augustus Frederick John Murray, Duke of, 1814-1864, 1846 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Atkinson, Henry Tindal, d.1890?, 1852 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Atlay, James, Bp. of Hereford, 1817- 1894, 1868-72, undated (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Auckland, Robert John Eden, Baron, Bp. of Bath and Wells, 1799-1870, 1850-60, undated (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Augusta, Duchess of Saxe-Coburg- Saalfeld, 1757-1831, undated (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Augusta Wilhelmina Louisa, Duchess of Cambridge, 1799-1889, 1864, undated (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Augusta Katherine (Gordon-Lennox), Princess Edward of Saxe-Weimar, d. 1904, undated (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Augustus Frederick, Duke of Sussex, 1773-1843, undated (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Avebury, John Lubbock, Baron, 1834-1913
    Related Archival Materials note
    See: Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913, box 39, folders 1379-1380
  - Ayres, Ruby M. (Ruby Mildred), 1883- 1955, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Ayrton, Acton Smee, 1816-1886, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Babington, Charles Cardale, 1808-1895, undated (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Baden-Powell of Gilwell, Robert Stephenson Smyth Baden-Powell, Baron, 1857-1941, undated (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Baggallay, Sir Richard, 1816-1888, 1880, undated (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Bailey, E. H., 1852 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Bailey, Thomas John, b. 1842, 1882 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Baines, Edward, Sir, 1800-1890, 1864 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Baines, Matthew Talbot, 1799-1860, 1854 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Baird, Dorothea, 1873-1933, 1896, undated (Box 4, Folder 128-129)
  - Baker, Benjamin, Sir, 1840-1907, 1892, undated (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Baker, Nicholas, 1845, undated (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Baker, William, 1841-1910, 1881 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Balfour, Jabez Spencer, b. 1843, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Ball, Robert S. (Robert Stawell), Sir, 1840-1913, 1899-1910, undated (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Ballantine, James, 1808-1877, undated (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Bancroft, Marie Effie Wilton, Lady, 1839-1926, undated (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Bancroft, Squire, 1841-1926, 1883-1910, undated (Box 5, Folder 137-138)
  - Baring, Charles Thomas, 1807-1879, 1856-62, undated (Box 5, Folder 139-142)
  - Baring, Walter, 1844-1915, undated (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Barnard, Frederick, 1846-1896, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Barnes, William Pemberton, 1856 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Barnett, Morris, 1800-1856, undated (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Barrett, Wilson, 1848-1904, 1885-1903, undated (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Barrington, Lady Caroline (Grey), 1799-1875, undated (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Barrington, George William Barrington, Viscount, 1824-1886, 1881 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Barrington, Rutland, 1853-1922, undated (Box 5, Folder 150-151)
  - Bass, Harriet Georgina (Thornewill), Lady, d. 1931, 1886 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Bass, Michael T. (Michael Thomas), 1799-1884, 1853 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Bate, C. Spence (Charles Spence), 1818- 1889, 1860 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Bateman, Thomas, 1821-1861, 1855 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Bates, Henry Walter, 1825-1892, 1865-90 (Box 5, Folder 156-157)
  - Bates, Thomas, 1775-1849, 1839 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Bath, Frances Isabella Catherine (Vesey) Thynne, Marchioness of, 1840- 1915, 1868 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Bath, John Alexander Thynne, Marquis of, 1831-1896, 1866-87 (Box 5, Folder 160-161)
  - Bathe, Lily (Langtry) de, 1852-1929
    See: Langtry, Lily, 1852-1929, box 37, folder 1317
  - Bathurst, Seymour Henry Bathurst, Earl of, 1864-1943, 1901-04 (Box 5, Folder 162-163)
  - Battersea, Lady (Constance), 1843-1931, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Bauer, Ethel, 1899-1903 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Baxendale, John, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Baxter, David, Sir, 1793-1872, 1863 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Bayly, Ada Ellen, 1857-1903, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Bayning, Henry William-Powlett, Baron, 1797-1866, 1827-40 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Beaconsfield, Benjamin Disraeli, Earl of, 1804-1881, undated (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Beale, Dorothea, 1831-1906, undated (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Beatrice, Princess, Consort of Henry, Prince of Battenberg, 1857-1944, 1913-24, undated (Box 6, Folder 172-173)
  - Beauchamp, Frederick Lygon, Earl, 1830-1891, 1884 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Beaufort, Emily Frances (Smith) Somerset, Duchess of, ca. 1800-1889, 1840 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Beaufort, Georgiana Charlotte (Curzon- Howe) Somserset, Duchess of, 1825-1906, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Beaufort, Henry Adelbert Wellington FitzRoy Somerset, Duke of, 1847-1924, undated (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Beaufort, Henry Charles FitzRoy Somerset, Duke of, 1824-1899, 1871-97 (Box 6, Folder 178-181)
  - Beazley, Samuel, 1786-1851, 1828 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Beck, Edmund, 1880, undated (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Beck, Edward Anthony, 1896-97 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Beck, S. Adams, 1876-80 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Becker, E., 1855-59 (Box 6, Folder 186-187)
  - Beckles, Edward Hyndman, Bp. of Sierra Leone, 1816-1902, 1880 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Bedford, Lady Elizabeth (Sackville- West) Russell, Duchess of, 1818-1897, 1885 (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Bedford, Francis Charles Hastings Russell, Duke of, 1819-1891, 1886 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Bedford, Herbrand Arthur Russell, Duke of, 1858-1940, 1894-1905, undated (Box 6, Folder 191-193)
  - Bedford, Mary du Caurroy (Tribe) Russell, Duchess of, 1865-1937, 1903, undated (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Bedford, Paul John, ca. 1792-1871, 1864, undated (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Beeching, H. C. (Henry Charles), 1859- 1919, 1902 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Beere, Fanny Mary (Whitehead) Dering, 1856-1915, 1884, undated (Box 6, Folder 197-198)
  - Bell, Evans, 1825-1887, 1873-78 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Bell, George Charles, 1832-1913, undated (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Bell, I. Lowthian (Isaac Lowthian), 1816-1904, undated (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Bell, James, 1824-1908, 1854 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Bell, John, 1764-1836, 1824 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Bell, Thomas, 1792-1880, undated (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Bellew, Harold Kyrle, 1855-1911, 1883, undated (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Belloc, Bessie Rayner, 1829-1925, 1858 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Bell-Smith, Frederic Marlett, 1846- 1923, 1894, undated (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Benham, W. Gurney (William Gurney), Sir, 1859-1944, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Bennett, William J.E. (William James Early), 1804-1886, 1856, undated (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Bennet-Poë, I. T., undated (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Benson, Arthur Christopher, 1862-1925, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Benson, Edward White, 1829-1896, 1879-95, undated (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic), 1867- 1940, 1911, undated (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Benson, Francis Robert, Sir, 1858-1939, 1900, undated (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Benson, Mary (Sidgwick), b. 1859, d. after 1896, 1877 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Benson, Robert Hugh, 1871-1914, undated (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Bentinck, George Cavendish, 1821-1891, 1840-71, undated (Box 6, Folder 217-218)
  - Beresford, Mr., 1846 (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - Beresford, Charles William de la Poer Beresford, Baron, 1846-1919, 1898, undated (Box 7, Folder 220)
  - Beresford Hope, A.J.B. (Alexander James Beresford), 1820-1887, 1851-81, undated (Box 7, Folder 221-224)
  - Bernal Osborne, Ralph, 1808-1882, 1830-54 (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - Bernard, J. H. (John Henry), 1860-1927, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - Bernard, Montague, 1820-1882, undated (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - Bernard, William Bayle, 1807-1875, 1873, undated (Box 7, Folder 228-229)
  - Bessborough, John William Ponsonby, Earl of, 1781-1847, undated (Box 7, Folder 230)
  - Bessborough, Edward Ponsonby, Earl of, 1851-1920, 1895 (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - Best, Edna, 1900-1974, undated (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Betham-Edwards, Matilda, 1836-1919, undated (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Beverley, William Roxby, 1824-1889, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Bickersteth, Robert, 1816-1884, 1859-75, undated (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Biddulph, Michael Anthony Shrapnel, Sir, 1823-1900, 1875-1904, undated (Box 7, Folder 236-237)
  - Biddulph, Robert, Sir, 1835-1918, undated (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Biddulph, Thomas Myddleton, Sir, 1809- 1878, 1866-77 (Box 7, Folder 239-243)
  - Bidwell, Henry N., undated (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Billington, John, b. 1830, 1868, undated (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Billington, N., b. 1826, undated (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Binney, Edward William, 1812-1881, 1840 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Binney, Thomas, 1798-1874, 1850-74, undated (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Birch, Mr., 1816 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Birch, H. M., 1820-1884, 1850, undated (Box 7, Folder 250-251)
  - Birdwood, George C. M. (George Christopher Molesworth), Sir, 1832- 1917, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Birkbeck, George, 1776-1841, undated (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Birrell, Augustine, 1850-1933, 1890, undated (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Bispham, David Scull, 1857-1921, 1902, undated (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Black, Charles E.D., 1885 (Box 8, Folder 256)
  - Blain, Helen (Barry), undated (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Blessington, Marguerite, Countess of, 1789-1849, 1841, undated (Box 8, Folder 258)
  - Blewitt, Octavian, 1810-1884, 1851 (Box 8, Folder 259)
  - Blomfield, Charles James, 1786-1857, 1822-55, undated (Box 8, Folder 260-264)
  - Bloomfield, Benjamin Bloomfield, Baron, 1768-1846, 1800 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Bloomfield, Georgiana (Liddell) Bloomfield, Baroness, 1822-1905, undated (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Blouët, Leon Paul, 1848-1903
    See: O'Rell, Max, 1848-1903, box 44, folder 1603
  - Bloxam, John Rouse, 1807-1891, 1870 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Blumenthal, Jacques, 1829-1908, undated (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Blunt, Arthur Cecil, 1843-1896, 1874-93, undated (Box 8, Folder 269-271)
  - Blunt, John Henry, 1823-1884, 1868 (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Blunt, John J. (John James), 1794-1855, 1844 (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Blythswood, Archibald Campbell Campbell, Baron, 1835-1908, 1886 (Box 9, Folder 274)
  - Bonnet, Charles, 1720-1793, undated (Box 9, Folder 275)
  - Booth, Sarah, 1793-1867, 1836 (Box 9, Folder 276)
  - Borchgrevink, C. E. (Carsten Egebert), 1864-1934, 1896 (Box 9, Folder 277)
  - Borthwick, P. (Peter) 1804-1852, undated (Box 9, Folder 278)
  - Bosanquet, Helen Dendy, 1860-1925, 1898-1903, undated (Box 9, Folder 279)
  - Boucicault, Dion, 1820-1890, undated (Box 9, Folder 280)
  - Boucicault, Dion, 1859-1929, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 281)
  - Boulenger, George Albert, 1858-1937, 1883 (Box 9, Folder 282)
  - Bourchier, Arthur, 1863-1927, 1901-08, undated (Box 9, Folder 283-284)
  - Bourke, Henry Beresford, 1855-1921, undated (Box 9, Folder 285)
  - Bowerbank, James Scott, 1797-1877, undated (Box 9, Folder 286)
  - Bowles, Thomas Gibson, 1841-1922, 1887-94 (Box 9, Folder 287-288)
  - Bowring, John, Sir, 1792-1872, 1837-64, undated (Box 9, Folder 289-290)
  - Bowyer, George, 1811-1883, 1862, undated (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Boyd, Archibald, 1803-1883, undated (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Boyd-Carpenter, Annie Maude (Gardner), 1897 (Box 9, Folder 293)
  - Boyd-Carpenter, William, Bp. of Ripon, 1841-1918, 1884-1911, undated (Box 9, Folder 294)
  - Boyne, Leonard, 1852-, 1908, undated (Box 9, Folder 295)
  - Bradford, Orlando George Charles Bridgeman, Earl of, 1819-1898, 1880, undated (Box 10, Folder 296)
  - Bradley, George Granville, 1821-1903, 1880-89, undated (Box 10, Folder 297)
  - Braithwaite, Dame Florence Lilian, 1873-1948, 1915 undated (Box 10, Folder 298)
  - Brampton, Henry Hawkins, Baron, 1817- 1907, 1883-94, undated (Box 10, Folder 299-300)
  - Brandram, Samuel, 1821-1892, 1880-81 (Box 10, Folder 301-302)
  - Brassey, Annie Allnutt, Baroness, 1839-1887, 1885 (Box 10, Folder 303)
  - Brassey, Thomas Brassey, Earl, 1836- 1918, 1890-98, undated (Box 10, Folder 304-305)
  - Brayley, E. W. (Edward William), 1802- 1870, 1835 (Box 10, Folder 306)
  - Brayton, Lily, b. 1876, undated (Box 10, Folder 307)
  - Breadalbane, John Campbell, Marquis of, 1796-1862, 1831-57, undated (Box 10, Folder 308-309)
  - Brewer, Ebenezer Cobham, 1810-1897, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 310)
  - Brewer, J. H., 1846, undated (Box 10, Folder 311)
  - Brewer, J. S. (John Sherren), 1810-1879, 1873 (Box 10, Folder 312)
  - Brewster, David, Sir, 1781-1868, undated (Box 10, Folder 313)
  - Bridge, Frederick, Sir, 1844-1924, undated (Box 10, Folder 314)
  - Bridport, Alexander Nelson Hood, Viscount, 1814-1904, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 315)
  - Bright, James Franck, 1832-1920, 1887-1912 (Box 10, Folder 316-317)
  - Bright, John, 1811-1889, 1852-87 (Box 10, Folder 318)
  - Bright, William, 1824-1901, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 319)
  - Bristol, Frederick William John Hervey, Marquess, 1834-1907, 1893, undated (Box 10, Folder 320)
  - Bristol, Lady, d. 1927, undated (Box 10, Folder 321)
  - Broadley, Alexander Meyrick, 1847-1916, 1884 (Box 11, Folder 322)
  - Brock, William, 1807-1875, undated (Box 11, Folder 323)
  - Brodrick, Alan, Hon., 1840-1909, 1864 (Box 11, Folder 324)
  - Brooks, Shirley, 1815-1874, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 325)
  - Brough, Fanny, 1865-1950
    See: Marlowe, Julia, 1865-1950, box 40, folders 1430-1431
  - Brough, Lionel, 1836-1909, 1886, undated (Box 11, Folder 326-328)
  - Brougham and Vaux, Henry Brougham, Baron, 1778-1868, 1843-55 (Box 11, Folder 329-330)
  - Broughton, John Cam Hobhouse, Baron, 1786-1869, 1827-49, undated (Box 11, Folder 331-335)
  - Broughton, Julia Tomlinson (Hay) Hobhouse, Lady, d. 1835, undated (Box 11, Folder 336)
  - Broughton, Phyllis, undated (Box 11, Folder 337)